It's important that there
is a place where there is?.
If you want it, I will protect you!.
It's okay, let's go ahead and go ahead!.
The moon will always come to the moon!.
The moon will come to the moon!.
Let's look at the light of the stars?.
We'll see
you next time.
Go, go, go!
You're right! We won!
We won!
I'm so happy!
You won!
He's so big! He's mine!
You can't have him!
Stop!
Daddy!
Thank you! Awesome!
Those guys are amazing! Bravo!
Bravo!
He's so big!
He's mine!
Oh, man, I've moved to tears.
Give it your best in the
third round, too. Shut up!
Who's sad are you on anyway, you traitors?
I can't believe this.
Nobody's ever beaten the Krieg monsters.
Oh, hi, ref. Wakey-wakey.
Hey, you better make your
call. Go ahead. Here.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, that last move was a flagrant
foul if I've ever seen one.
He's out of the game.
And that's the final whistle!
There you have it, folks.
The groggy ring match is officially over.
It's the end of an era.
The groggy monsters have
finally been dethroned.
As the kings of the ring.
Our new champions and
winners of the second round.
are Zoro and Sanji of
the Skullhut Pirates!
What'd you think would happen?
Like our guys would never lose to you!
Hey, Nami!
Hey, Robin!
Was I great?
Huh, was I?
You were just wonderful.
You're nothing but a jerk!
Don't scare me like that!
Hey, hey, stop.
I'm so glad you followed
my plan after all!
You really think you had
something to do with this?
Now,
as I'm sure you all know,
at the end of our fight,
our winners, the Straw Hat Pirates,
can claim their hard-earned prize!
Will they take a member of Foxy's crew,
or will they take his Jolly Roger?
Either way, it's up to their
captain and their captain alone!
Now, drumroll, please!
Well, the choice is obvious, isn't it?
You mean he's going to pick me?
I get it.
They want me, don't they?
They've wanted me this
whole time. My heart.
My heart isn't ready to
say farewell yet. Oh, no.
He's looking this way.
He's gonna take me.
I know it.
I bet it'll be me.
So long, guys.
I don't want to go.
I'll put a smile on my face for my
friends, even if I'm crying on the inside.
Curses.
Why do I have to be so lovable?
Come on, Luffy, please.
OK, I choose. Hold on a sec.
What's up, Nami?
Think about it.
Their boss is probably going to
take part in the next round, right?
Sure, we'd all like to get Chopper back.
But if we end up losing the next round,
then they'll probably take him right back?
and our win would go to waste.
And since his crew will be dumbstruck
when they lose their precious boss?
we're guaranteed to keep
him for good, get it?
No, say it isn't so.
They're really gonna
take our captain away?
But that's the peanut strategy.
You guys are the lowest of the low.
Go home, lousy peanuters.
Are you afraid to fight us fair?
Although there's no rule
against this strategy,
it certainly seems a bit underhanded.
A little cheating is expected of pirates,
but suddenly taking a cruise
captain away in the middle
of a game is no different
than running from a fight.
Shame!
Shame on you Straw Hats
and shame on the heartless
devil of a woman who
came up with this plan!
You're truly a nefarious navigator, Nami!
How dare you talk trash about Nami!
I Outta fillet you!
Why are they so mean?
Well, even if it doesn't
go against the rules,
it does seem to go against some
of their pirate sensibilities.
I'm with Nami on this one!
I don't know.
I think they're right.
Nami, why don't you grow a backbone?
You're just making a big
fuss because you lost.
How about you shut up and deal with it?
Yes, ma 'am, we're sorry!
Underhanded witch, though
she is, the girl is right.
Monkey D.
Loopy is the captain of the winning team,
so it's up to him to decide
how this battle will unfold.
That is to say, he's free to choose
anyone he likes, including Foxy himself.
This is it.
He's picking me for sure.
No matter how you slice it, I'm
the only choice that makes sense.
So they're gonna pick me, huh?
I knew these guys were cool.
Say, just a quick thought.
That plan of yours, although it
would give us a big advantage,
you realize it would also make
Foxy a part of our crew. Uh...
Yeah, I think I'll pass. Whoa!
Now that the Straw Hats are done
emotionally abusing our boss,
it's time for them to make their decision.
Come on, don't leave us
in suspense any longer.
Fine.
In that case, there's
someone I want to take back.
Come on, Chopper, get over here!
Dad, you better know me that time!
I'll miss you, Choppy!
I was so scared!
I'm so happy you won!
Are you kidding?
Bunch of suckers like that
could never beat my crew.
Oh!
Our sweet captain's heart has been crushed
under the weight of those cruel words!
It's one thing to turn him down, but
did they have to do it like that?
Aw, it's OK.
Even if they don't want you, we still do.
You're always welcome here.
Do you mean it?
Nobody makes fun of our
boss and gets away with it.
Yeah, you'll see.
We'll get him next round.
We won't let you down, boss, I promise.
We love you.
Don't leave us, you guys.
Thank you.
I promise I'll never leave.
You're the only crew for me.
Cut the crap, will ya?
Just as a fair warning, nobody has ever
been able to beat me in the combat round.
Oh, yeah?
You think you can beat me in a fight?
Maybe so, and maybe not.
But this isn't a fight, my boy.
It's a game.
One, two, three!
Rick finally arrives at the combat round!
But before we start, we must
decide on the battlefield!
The two competitors spin
this unbiased cannon,
and wherever it stops is the
place where they'll do combat!
The match hasn't even started yet,
and you guys are cheating already?
There you have it!
The battlefield has been set!
And would you look at that!
By sheer coincidence, it's
on the deck of the Sexy Foxy!
Oh, now you're just rubbing
it in, you little liar!
Moving right along, let's
explain the rules of combat!
Everything within 50 meters
of where the cannonball
landed is considered
part of the battlefield.
In other words, it's a 100-meter-wide circle
measuring from the center of the ship.
Weapons and anything else found inside
the designated battlefield are allowed.
However, outside crew members are
strictly forbidden from entering the ship.
Knock your opponent out of
bounds and you win the match.
Simple as that.
Also, as long as you're in the circle
fighting in the air or water is fine.
Foxy, Foxy!
While we're busy preparing
for the main event,
Porch's lovely flower cheerleaders
are performing on the stage.
If that's not your thing,
you can also check out a warm-up match
being held on the front of the ship.
And as always,
our Association of Stulls is selling a
limited edition Davey-backed
bite merchandise.
So be sure to check that out as well.
Nobody wants your junk.
Just start the match already.
And here you go, fellas, two
limited edition Foxy Pins.
Haven't you seen enough of his young face?
We're ready.
Where's your captain at?
He's right there.
Now take him before he
buys something else.
Why do I have to pay so much for
your crappy popcorn and cola?
If you don't like the price,
how about you don't buy it?
Give me 50 % off.
Get out of here.
That cannon means the
preparations are complete.
So if the opening entertainment
could please leave the stage.
Thank you.
And now it's time for the main event.
The fighters are in place and
the bell is ready to sound.
Grab a seat in the spectator
stands before it's too late.
Now that's odd.
It's cloudy all of a sudden.
Today we have a real treat,
ladies and gentlemen.
A Captain vs.
Captain Showdown!
First in the left corner, we
have a reigning Davey McChampion!
A man among men who never
turns down a challenge
that boasts a legendary
combat record of 920 wins!
Our one and only boss,
the Silver Fox Boxer!
You listen up, Luffy,
and you listen up good.
You ain't your old self no more.
You put that boy to bed, and now
you're gone and woken up a man.
Just like that hairstyle's
woken up your wild side.
Since the dawn of time, man has
wondered if the champion makes the afro,
or the afro makes the champion.
But that's a question even
modern science can't answer.
Now listen, with that afro on your head,
your fists are weapons of mass destruction.
Strawhead's too scared to come out!
I bet he ran away!
And in the right corner, our challenger!
Hailing from the east blue
with a tiny crew of only seven!
And a massive 100 million fairy bounty,
The rubber wonder they call Strahd,
Mountain Davey! Yeah!
Yeah!
Wow, Luffy is sporting a larger-than-life
afro with a personality to match.
Yeah, looking sharp, buddy.
That's messed up.
Wow, Luffy's cooler than ever.
I agree.
The fighters have entered the battlefield
and look like they're ready to rumble!
Now that Luffy has turned in
his Straw Hat for a mighty afro,
does he have the power to protect the pride
of his crew and unborn children alike?
Or will Foxy's undefeated fist strip
him of all his hopes and dreams?
Only time will tell as
this fateful final round
of the Davy Mac fight
explodes into action!
What's all that stuff?
This is the dressing room.
You got to wear boxing gloves, but
pretty much anything else goes.
This is awesome!
This place is more like a costume
shop than a dressing room, you know?
Man, I can't pick a favorite.
Do you think it'd be okay if
I just wore all of it at once?
Hey, what about this?
Am I cool now?
No.
This is it.
Hey, Straw Hat, I'm really
diggin' the new lug!
I mean, Usa, pull a quick
bait with your left!
Then slap that chin with
a golden uppercut! Yeah!
So funky, I can feel that child
lightin' a fire in my soul!
You see, this is what happens when
you leave Luffy alone with Usa.
Let me try to show some dignity.
You might be the champ, but
this one's got some bite!
He's out of sight!
You best get ready to fight!
Because this one-two punch
is going to give you up.
All right, Corner Man.
It's time to take your
sideshow to the sidelines.
I was really getting my groove on.
You can't make me leave already.
Manager out.
Get off with the show.
And since I'm not needed here
either, I'll be on my merry way.
Let's get this and started.
What the?
The stands are moving.
Whoa. Cool.
I got to get chairs like that on my ship.
Now then, Luffy, what do you
say you and I have a little fun?
This whole ship is our
playground, after all.
Feel free to go as wild as you like!
Don't worry, we have plenty of skilled
shipwrights to clean up after our mess.
Now the opponents face off atop the
fabulous figurehead of the sexy Foxy!
Which was chosen by sheer
coincidence, of course!
What kind of fearsome flying
fists will be unfurled today?
Get him, boss!
You can't let that
winning streak stop now!
Luffy, don't lose!
That's all that matters!
Just watch out for his beam, OK?
Excitement fills the stands in the
final seconds before the match.
It's plunder or be plundered. Luffy!
Go boss!
It's the Silver Slow Slow Slugger
versus the Gum-Gum Jatling Gun.
This is a one-round
bout with no time limit.
As long as they stay in
bounds, Everything goes!
The fighters are ready!
And there goes the bell!
Yeah, you! Go on to go!
Slow, slow, me!
My arm is fast, but my fist is all slow!
You don't expect me to be
afraid of a rubber hose, do you?
Give me a sec!
Come back!
Slow, slow, baby!
I fooled you!
That's me!
Wow, he's floating.
I guess that means he falls slow, too.
I told him to watch out for that.
Why won't he listen to me?
I know there's no time limit, but come on!
Why don't you spare us both and give up?
No way!
Nine tails around!
Oh!
Our boss on Gleasius' signature
attack right off the bat!
Stronghead is helpless to fight back!
This is crazy.
He's not budging an inch.
No, look closely.
He's just moving in slow motion.
Consider that a preview of what's to come,
though, to your credit, it seems like
you can take a punch pretty well.
Fortunately, I've got plenty
of other tricks up my sleeve.
Come back here.
Well, your 30 seconds are about up.
He's falling overboard. No, baby!
That slow, slow beam is going to
give me more trouble than I thought.
Wow, beams sure are cool, huh?
Still, I've got to be more careful
where I stretch my arms now.
Where'd that jerk run off to, anyway?
I won't let you sneak up on
me with your beam, Splithead!
Come on and fight like a man!
I understand your frustration,
but don't take it out on the air!
Did he use his beam?
Welcome to the sexy boxy, Rubber Boy.
That was a dirty trick.
He got me!
Just calm down for a second, will ya?
Can't you see I'm trying to
show you some hospitality here?
Those cannonballs are
moving in slow-mo, too.
Well, if you can ride
on one, then so can't I!
Be careful, kid!
I wouldn't touch that one if I were you!
Ah, and that one, too.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Can't say I didn't warn you!
What's his problem anyway?
If he keeps this up, he's
gonna sink his own ship.
I'll sink you first!
Slow, slow, foxy-faced bomb tenor!
Creepy!
Huh? Oh, they're pins.
They sure are a lot bigger
than the one I bought, though.
Of course we're bigger, stupid.
That's because we're bomb-stupid.
Wait, what?
Did you say bomb?
Why is a bomb talking?
I'm the real thing, that's why!
My punches weren't quite doing the trick.
So I upgraded my gloves, see?
Oh, and fair warning, those
bombs are about to go off.
Yeah! Body blue! Body blue!
Oh, it's Usopp.
Hey, what's going on with
the fight down there?
Uh, I don't have a clue.
Are you kidding me?
A series of powerful
explosions rocks our ship!
Which just so happens
to be the battlefield!
The likely cause of some foxy merchandise
that just happens to be explosive!
All this cheating just so
happens to be pissing me off.
No wonder that jerk's never lost a match.
Loopy, speak to me!
Hey, sit down.
Using his surroundings to his advantage,
our boss slammed Straw Hat head-on with
a strategically placed cannon attack.
All I can see is smoke.
Was Straw Hat blown to smithereens?
That was a close one.
Indeed, Foxy's onslaught was...
Shut up! You're annoying!
That's a miracle!
Shawhat Luffy is alive!
Whoa, he's alive!
There's no way!
He somehow abated the explosive
attack at point-blank range!
What amazing speed!
The 100 million Barry Rubber
Boy is truly a thing of wonder!
At the power of the frog!
Hurry it up, Luffy!
Uh-oh!
It looks like our boss's next
attack is already underway!
What could it be plotting this time?
The sneaky foxy lets out an unsettling
laugh from behind a thick screen of smoke.
Meanwhile, Straw Hat stares
cluelessly into the abyss.
The suspense is killing me!
Where is our boss hiding?
Is that him?
Oh, how'd you like that? You had enough?
You got blown up twice as bad as me!
Shut up, I'm fine! See?
Look!
You don't look fine at all!
I don't even want you on my crew anymore.
I'd rather just crush you.
Slow, slow me!
Gum, gum!
I'm going to break your arm so you
can't hit me with those dumb beads.
Ah!
Does this guy want to fight or not?
There you are!
Gotcha!
Huh?
It was just a cutout?
Slow, slow beam!
Hey, hey, hey! Now what?
Which one is the real me?
Which direction will the beam come from?
How should I know?
They all look the same, just a bunch of
split heads with stupid-looking haircuts.
Oh, now a stupid-looking split head?
That one!
You jerk!
I may be a cheater, but
at least I have a heart!
You're in for it now! Look up!
Ah!
Damn it! A trap door!
That's what you get for keeping
your head in the clouds!
You're the one who told me to
look up in the first place!
So I did!
Better look down, too!
Why is the floor moving?
Fuck! It's Loopy!
If he falls in the water, he's done for!
Come on, you can't let
the fight ends this way!
You can get rid of me that easy!
Close call!
It wouldn't be any fun if Boss
knocked him out right off the bat.
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
After power!
This ship's a pain in
the butt! What gives?
Hey, Splithead, where'd you go?
What happened here?
Straw Hat's narrow escape didn't
seem to impress this foxy pin.
You might even say it's laughing at him.
So there you are.
The cabin of the ship
is Foxy's playground.
Will Luffy be lured inside?
Hold on, Luffy, it's a trap.
Whatever you do, do not go in that ship.
I'm going to beat that jerk's brains out.
Straw Hat throws caution to the
wind and dashes inside the ship.
Unfortunately, that means I can't
give you play-by-play anymore.
But I think it's safe to
assume that whatever's
going on in there is completely amazing.
But leave!
It's time to put those
wings to the Tesla bird!
So spread them and fly!
These seats are bad enough
without you standing in the way.
Cool. A gun deck.
It's huge, too.
Too bad Usopp isn't here.
He'd love this.
Now, where'd Foxy run off to?
Aha! He's over there!
All right, good.
He's coming after me.
And now he'll come rushing
through that door like an idiot
But we'll see how chipper our
little rubber boy is Who in my
room full of two-foot steel spikes
makes Swiss cheese out of him
Come on, Straw Hat, you know you won
Hey, it's him Wow, wonder
what that room's used for.
What kind of monster fires off
cannons inside someone else's ship?
At least he stopped running away.
You brain die!
I'll show you, just wait.
No way!
Come back and fight me!
Doesn't he have any
common decency, honestly?
I've had enough foxy-faced transformation.
I got you now!
Who's that?
Dear me, are you ill?
Tell me where it hurts and I'll fix it.
Is it your head? Is that it?
Are you sick in the head?
Wait a sec.
Did you see someone
else come through here?
Why, no, I didn't see a soul.
But never mind that.
You broke something, didn't you?
You had a face?
I could have sworn I saw
him go in there. Hold on.
That weird lady, she looked just like him.
I get it.
Hey, you must be Foxy's sister.
You can't fool me.
It's Hunter Foxy. No!
What the heck is this?
So that's it!
She lied to me so I
wouldn't fight her brother!
Is he even trying to fight anymore?
The kitchen!
Slice of the fish, what do you know?
You got some nice carpaccio.
Don't forget to cut a tarot.
Do-re-mi-fas-or-a-ti-do.
Ahem. Yes?
Have you seen some old
fox dude with his head
split in two that looks
really stupid and not cool?
You truly are heartless.
Hey, it's you!
And I was the woman in
the doctor's office, too?
What?
No way
Slow, slow, beam.
Nine tails.
I didn't just happen to
lure you into the kitchen!
It's all part of the plan.
That is to say, I have a surprise waiting
for you after my punches take effect.
Do you want to guess what it is?
It's nothing alive, at least.
That would be against
the rules, after all.
In case you haven't learned yet, once the
effect of my slow-snow beam wears off,
all those punches are
going to hit you at once.
That's it. Keep going.
You're only a couple of feet away
from your final wrestling place.
And that's 30 seconds.
Where'd he run off to now?
Turn around.
I'm right here.
What kind of costume is that?
It's not a costume,
it's a pilot's uniform.
And this is my robot,
a boxing masterpiece,
corrected and perfected
through countless trials.
Let me introduce you to the Gorilla Punch.
The only gorilla I see on it is you,
All right, we'll have to change that.
Wait, shut up.
Jeez, you're so rude.
Gorilla Punch, let's finish him.
How do you get that crazy
thing to move anyway?
It's a secret.
You sure are sweating a lot.
We are seeing things.
If you think you can
dodge, then be my guest.
But be warned, I won't
make it easy for you.
Slow, slow beam.
What the heck are you aiming at?
Take a look behind you.
Is someone there? It's a mirror.
Yes, and mirrors reflect slow-mo-booters.
I got you.
Nooo!
Oh, what's the matter?
Can't take the heat?
Did I forget to mention
these gloves burn like fire?
Cause they do!
Not even Sea Kings can stand
the beating from this thing!
Mirror Ratchet!
That's right that's for
me it's a beam and punch
combo i call this attack the
slow poke ball demon. This
is
a pain i gotta
find a way to get in closer.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You can't dodge forever!
What's it gonna be?
The beam or the machine?
Wait, that's it!
I never thought of that!
Oh, no!
Come, come!
Stop!
Little rat.
Get out of my golden hands.
Time marches on but neither
combatant has emerged
as a winner in the final
round of this Daily
back fight it's truly
unusual for someone to
last so long against
Foxy in his own territory
And the crowd cheers for our boss
with all their hearts Luffy won't lose
well that goes without Saying he's
Luffy and he has an afro I'd say being
Luffy should be more than enough though
The afro is nice okay you're gonna
have to explain this afro thing to me
you're all acting like it powers him up,
but that doesn't make any sense.
I think this is the longest
combat round I've ever seen.
The guy is made of rubber, after all.
He's made of rubber, and he has an afro.
Really?
Am I the only one who doesn't get this?
What's this?
It looks like something
is happening on the deck.
Who has the upper hand?
Or perhaps the battle is injured with
a bang and only one fighter remains.
No, wait.
I see dead people.
But only one of them is
standing! And it's... Yes!
Powerpuss!
Good job!
Meanwhile, it looks like Straw
Hat has been burned to a crisp!
He must have taken some
seriously hot punches!
No way!
No way.
It takes more than punches
to burn someone like that!
What gives?
Wait, look.
He's out! I can't stall!
I'm sure that is up!
It seemed like he was down for
the count, but the fight goes on!
You're persistent.
I'll give you that much, Rubber Boy.
It's Afro Power!
What else could it be?
Finish him, boss!
That's the slow beam sword
as I'm sure you can probably
tell I've restrained your arms
and legs good luck with that
That's 30 seconds.
He's down for sure this time.
No, not yet.
Come on.
He's up.
He's really up.
That's nuts.
Who is this guy?
They shouldn't have
let him have that afro.
Nobody can stop him now.
Stubborn brat.
Take this!
Another slush the beans!
Megaton Ninetales Rush!
That beam is for cheaters!
Try fighting like a man for once!
Sit down.
This looks like the end!
Dealing the punches ain't
so easy either, kid.
He's beating Lupi to death out there!
He's giving up again!
Whoa, he's tough!
I won't let you take a single member
of my crew, even if it kills me!
He's on his feet!
Straw Hat Luffy refuses to give it on!